Philipp Eibl

Profile

Currently pursuing a Computer Science Specialist with a focus on Artificial Intelligence at the University of Toronto. I work best in teams and love to take on new challenges. I am currently most interested in question answering and NLP as a whole.

Education

Bachelor of Science, University of Toronto, Toronto

September 2019 — Present

Computer Science Specialist (Focus in Artificial Intelligence)

Bachelor of Science, University of British Columbia, Kelowna

September 2019 — May 2019

Computer Science (Major), Data Science (Minor)

Summer school (2015), Harvard University, Boston

June 2015 — August 2015

Summer school (2014), Oxford Royale Academy, Oxford Programming Boot Camp (2016), Make School, Sunnyvale

Experience

Full Stack Development at Antimatter, Toronto

April 2019 — October 2019

Created large scale web apps for businesses from scratch using React.

Full Stack Development at the University of British Columbia, Kelowna

December 2018 — March 2019

Created an eCommerce-like website for a charitable research project.

Full Stack Web App Development at Metaplug.io, San Jose

May 2019 — August 2019

Worked on client dashboard, the database, web scraping and ML algorithm.

Mobile App Development at Deine Seite, Vienna

September 2019 — December 2019

Worked on a large-scale medical app, mostly in debugging and adding small features.

Extra-curricular activities

ML Engineer at Canadian Space Agency, Timmins

September 2019 — September 2019

ML model to analyze an image data set to detect muon frequency in the stratosphere.

Walnut Al: Text Summary Generator (k-Means Clustering)

November 2019 — Present

Airnotes: MacOs Notes App with +8K downloads

September 2019 — Present

Details

Toronto, Canada, (250) 258-6655 philipp.eibl@mail.utoronto.ca

Courses

NLP (2021)

Neural Networks (2021)

Intro to A.I (2021)

Probabilistic Learning/Reasoning (2021)

Computational Linguistics (2020)

Machine Learning (2020)

Data Structures & Algorithms

Enriched Statistics & Probability

Numerical Methods

Skills

NLP (language models, neural approaches, dependency parsing, ambiguity resolution)

ML/AI/Statistical Models (NN, Bayesian Models, GAN, ...)

OOP (Python, Java)

Data Science/ML (Numpy, Scipy,

PyTorch)

React (Redux, HTML, SASS, JS)

iOS Development (Swift)

Shell Scripting

Databases (MongoDB, SQL, Firebase)

Links

linkedin.com/in/philippeibl github.com/philippnoah philippnoah.com antimatter.studio (deprecated)

Languages

English

German

French

Italian